so
good afternoon everyone i'm adrika and
now
it's finally time for our uh
second last question uh
you know it's our last day of the quiz
show today
and it is the last second question after
this
only the only one question will be
coming
at five which will be our last question
and uh and this question question number
four
of the day it is our second last
question
so uh so just don't miss this
opportunity and just quickly answer this
question
so now without wasting any more time
let's just quickly start with our
question
so you are in hurry and need to cross a
road
with an underpass you will
a avoid underpass as
it saves time b avoid the underpass
and directly cross the road c
avoid underpass as it takes longer
or d avoid the underpass to cross the
road
so you know basically in this question
uh
we are asking that uh that you know you
are in a hurry you have to go
somewhere and you need to cross the road
but you are in a hurry and to cross the
road there is a
underpass so what will you do you will
avoid the underpass
or you will use the underpass so what
will you do
avoid underpass as it saves time
b avoid the underpass and directly cross
the road
or see avoid underpass as it takes
longer
or d avoid the underpass to cross the
road
uh or d avail the underpass to cross the
road here so
uh you know basically in this question
uh
we can learn a lot with each question
and
if we talk about this specific question
we are knowing about pedestrians
because the roads they are for everyone
not only the drivers but also for the
pedestrians
so this question it is uh in case you
are a pedestrian you know
if you you're a pedestrian you are in a
hurry and you need to cross the road
with an underpass so what will you do
you will avoid the underpass or you will
avail the underpass
so you know with this uh
okay so this is our
[Music]
you know there are options is you will
avoid underpass
as it saves time or we avoid underpass
and directly cross the road
c avoid underpass as it takes longer
or d avail avail
the underpass to cross the
so just think about it and answer this
question as soon as possible
uh this is our last day so
don't miss this opportunity uh until
make sure that our roads become safer
with these
simple step so now
you know so now stay tuned
for our road safety awareness session
by siam thank you so much everyone